{
    "id": "2ee818c26c0a4610aa412f1b74e07aa8",
    "title": "Sore, Pain, Hurt, Ache",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "cf2f891663bf4add8f6261ced0f96051",
            "title": "Ache, Pain, Hurt, Sore",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "I ............................... my knee while playing football yesterday.",
                    "description": "To hurt your knee is to injure it.",
                    "answers": [
                        "pained",
                        "ached",
                        "hurt"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "Gargling with warm water will relieve the symptoms of a ............................... throat.",
                    "description": "This is an example of a collocation. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "pain",
                        "hurt",
                        "sore"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "A dentist can fix that ....................................",
                    "description": "An ache is usually a mild discomfort that affects only a particular part of the body.\r\nPain is stronger.",
                    "answers": [
                        "ache",
                        "hurt",
                        "sore"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "The blow made my head ......................................",
                    "description": "An ache is usually a mild discomfort that affects only a particular part of the body.\r\nPain is stronger.",
                    "answers": [
                        "pain",
                        "ache",
                        "sore"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "The driver ....................................... himself badly in the accident.",
                    "description": "Hurt is usually used as a verb.",
                    "answers": [
                        "hurt",
                        "pained",
                        "ached",
                        "sored"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "These new shoes .....................................",
                    "description": "Hurt is usually a verb.",
                    "answers": [
                        "hurt",
                        "pain",
                        "ache"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "The boy came home with a ...................................... knee.",
                    "description": "A hurt knee is an injured knee.",
                    "answers": [
                        "paining",
                        "ached",
                        "hurt"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "The nurse bandaged my ..................................... toe.",
                    "description": "Like hurt, sore can also be an adjective. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "paining",
                        "hurting",
                        "sore"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "Losing the election was a .......................................... disappointment.",
                    "description": "This is an example of a collocation. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "paining",
                        "aching",
                        "sore"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "Put some iodine on that .......................................",
                    "description": "Sore can mean wound.",
                    "answers": [
                        "pain",
                        "sore",
                        "ache"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "The child's constant tantrums ......................................... his mother.",
                    "description": "Pained can mean agonized or distressed.",
                    "answers": [
                        "ached",
                        "pained",
                        "sored"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "I have a ..................................... in my shoulder.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "pain",
                        "ache",
                        "hurt"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}